Good day good
Добрый день
luck I just turned on Ukraine
удачи Только включил Украину
I just turned on Lithuania it
я только включил Литву
was just Israel Latvia And now
только что было Израиль Латвия А теперь
Lithuania She is from Ukraine the city
Литва Она из Украины город
you fly Russian Who by nationality
вы летать русский Кто по национальности
[music]
[музыка]
are Russians in these and then you need
на россиян в эти а потом тебе надо
goodness
благость
I don’t press them
я их не давлю
but don’t confuse to convince them with something  then there and so on.
но не путай убедить чем-то там так далее
I just ask
Я просто спрашиваю
sometimes I ask provocative if I
иногда спрашиваю провокационные если
see that the Major is already sitting, and so I ask
вижу что уже Майор сидит а так спрашиваю
Well, what can there be to stagger to
Ну что может что-то там до шатать до
these brains,
этих мозгов
not many people say that it makes no sense to
не многие говорят что не имеет смысла с
talk to them and you don’t stagger anything, I don’t
ними говорить и ничего не до шатаешься я
think everything  that there is a certain
все на считаю что есть определенные
segment of the audience to which it can reach
сегмент аудитории до который может дойти
which little by little it comes somewhere their
до который понемножку доходит где-то их
thoughts are shifted anyway in some
мысли они смещаются все равно в какую-то
direction So it’s right to
сторону Так что это правильно надо
say it is necessary to convince because
говорить надо переубеждать потому что
I will say So I am convinced that this should be
я скажу Так я убежден что это надо
done only because I  when in 14 I
делать только потому что я когда в 14
started working against Russian
году начал работать против российской
propaganda, well, in the Western
пропаганды уже ну на Западной скажем так
country of Europe, let's say, there are states and so on,
стране Европы там штаты и так далее я
then I told people look what they
тогда говорил людям посмотрите что они
are doing, well, not just a
делают это же ну не просто
taxi in Crimea and the war in Donbass and so on,
такси Крыма и война Донбассе и так далее
this is just the beginning I just showed there
это только начало Я показывал просто там
all sorts of memes there, etc., but sometime
мемчики всякие там так далее но когда-то
I look, I have a collection, I look at
я смотрю у меня есть коллекция я смотрю
all these pictures
эти все картиночки
[music]
[музыка]
Russians are like that Well, a little drunkards but
россияне такие Ну немножко пьяницы но
cool
крутые
and so on they
было все неоднозначный и так далее на
looked at me like this God, another
меня смотрели такие Боже еще один
crazy one found some kind of
какой-то сумасшедший нашелся какие-то
Internet pictures shows and when
интернетные картинки показывает а когда
you talk look
говоришь смотри
in these anonymous resources there Millions of
в этих ресурсах анонимных там Миллионы
people watch it every day
людей каждый день это смотрят
and there is just such a
и там просто идет такой
stream of this dirt and in general without
поток этой грязи а вообще без
competition
конкуренции
they even understand  these pictures are so it’s a
они понимаете даже вот эти картинки так
meme it’s all part of the
это ж вот мемчик это все часть
informational guilt they do they form
информационной вины они делают формируют
either some kind of positive image or
либо какой-то имидж позитивный либо у
some category has a negative image on the contrary
какой-то категории имеешь наоборот
or makes fun of a serious
негативный либо высмеивает серьезную
thing they translate it as a joke so that it is not
вещь переводят на шутку чтобы она не
perceived by people we just live in a
воспринималась людьми мы просто живем в
new reality and  we didn’t fully
новой реальности и мы до конца не
realize how much this affects us on
осознали насколько это влияет на нас на
society
общество
And so I
И вот я
do what I do because I believe
делаю то что я делаю потому что я верю
that Every drop of what and this is
что Каждая капля что
yours I
а это ваше
see a symbol so but there that I am one
вижу символ так но там что я один на
millitar tabur or something I don’t know what
миллитар табур или что-то я не знаю что
it means below the inscription of the
это означает внизу надпись
name
имени
[music]
[музыка]
me
меня
and this is this one as the ruler This is the
а это вот этот самый как правитель Это
first
первый
or who is the
или кто он
president
президент
[music]
[музыка]
I need it as a gift
Мне его подарили
as a token of gratitude
как знак благодарность
in Ukraine have been
в Украине бывали
many times over the past year probably
много раз за прошлый год наверное
12 times or thirteen And where did they go
12 раз или Тринадцать А куда и заезжали
to Ukraine
в Украину
Well, they started as the majority 24
Ну начинали как большинство 24
drove people to the border Well I don’t know what to
возили людей границы Ну не знаю что
do At first I wanted to go to war at all That’s
делать Сначала вообще воевать хотел
when the region was announced that it
идти Вот когда регион объявили что
was being created, but since I have no
создается но так как у меня нету ни
experience, I’m not even in the military with health
опыта я не военных даже со здоровьем
[music  ]
[музыка]
can’t
не может
do anything else Well, so we started to
еще чем еще заняться Ну так мы начали
bring people from
возить людей
the border to Warsaw. We
границы Варшаву
just had to do something. The flow of
Просто чем-то надо было заняться поток
people was just crazy,
людей шел просто сумасшедший
and then, well, we started making some
вот а потом ну начали каких-то
acquaintances, finding there then
знакомства находить там потом
six hundred cassocks on there, we’ll rent trucks,
шестая сотни ряс на там снимем грузовики
not weights, these
не грузики эти
pickups  and then, naturally,
пикаптельки вот а потом естественно все
farther and farther away Kiev and even were so
дальше дальше Киев и до даже были так
close to Donetsk That we were told that
близко Донецка Что нам говорили что вот
this Home, you see, will go
это этот Home видите будет ехать
Yes, because they can already fire mortars there
Да потому что там уже могут минометами
when they liberated Kherson there with
были когда освобождали Херсон там с
your
вашими
artillerymen who work on axes
артиллеристами которые на топорах
They help Well in  in general, something like
работают Им помогает Ну в общем как-то
this,
так
write to me on Telegram so that I can
напишите мне в Telegram чтобы я вас
contact you well You know
контактами списались хорошо Вы знаете
my channel
мой канал
[music]
[музыка]
And there is mine or now
И там есть мой или вот сейчас вот
write me comments there, I will write to you
пишите мне там комментарии я вам напишу
in a personal message and then we will contact with this, it’s
в личку и с этим контактируем потом
interesting that
интересно
something lags me
что-то меня лагает
If suddenly the date turns off now, I just
Если вдруг отключится сейчас дату просто
found it so now
в нашла так сейчас
What is your name
Как вас зовут
through
через
or is
или
already used to speaking
уже привык говорить
[music]
[музыка]
in different languages ​​different different
в разных языках разные разные системы
sound systems so it turns out when you
звуков так и получается когда на одном
start saying your name in one language,
языке начинаешь говорить свое имя
after all, no, not so I already Yes, I
все-таки нет не так Я уже Да я
started
начался
ukrainian mova and we
украинскую мову и мы
[music]
[музыка]
switch from polish
переходить с польского
russian ukrainian
российского украинский
and me and well, as in russian and
и и у меня и Ну как по российской и вот
it was very hard, well, troshki
это было очень тяжело ну вот трошки
troshki already
трошки уже
know polish well, yes,
польский хорошо знаете да
it’s there Lithuania is more very often like
это там Литва больше очень часто типа
border 2 is also very strong
приграничный 2 тоже очень сильный там
goods there  exchange and
товар обмен и
a little different Soviet times I lived in
немножко иначе советское время я жил
general near the border
вообще у границы
the only television that could
единственное телевидение которое можно
be watched was Polish and purely because of
было смотреть это было польская и чисто
this I learned because we
из-за этого научился потому что у нас
hated Lithuania very much,
ненавидели очень
so I have always been an example, she was in the
Литва вот я всегда пример она была в
Soviet Union, this is the avant-garde of
Советском Союзе вот этим авангардом
leaving the Soviet Union  when other
выхода из Советского Союза когда другие
Republics looked with open eyes,
Республики смотрели открытыми глазами
something was being done in Lithuania, Lithuania was already
что-то делается в Литве Литва уже
worried, always the father was in the People’s
переживала всегда отец был в Народном
hand, it’s like you
руке это как у вас этот литовский
pity turned off this Lithuanian Yes, that is, Lithuania Yes,
жалко отключила да то есть Литва Да
Lithuania has always been Under the Soviet Union,
Литва всегда была При Советском Союзе
such an avant-garde, an
таким авангардом авангардом
anti-svechiny avant-garde, an avant-garde of the collapse of the Scoop, and
антисвечины авангардом развала Совка и
when in  at the end of the 80s, we still whispered
когда в конце 80-х у нас еще там шептали
yes there. In Lithuania, serious movements were already made,
да В Литве уже делали серьезные движения
serious rallies, so it’s a pity ours
серьезные митинги поэтому на жалко наши
ended. Well, I wrote down the contact, we are
оборвалась Ну я записал контакт мы
in contact
контактируем